《越狱》前情回顾
previously on prison break
－什么罪名 －故意谋杀
What are the charges?     Attempted murder.
他还因被控谋杀母亲和继父  而遭到法院传讯
He's also being arraigned for the murder of his mother and his stepfather.
不要像正义使者那样看我
Don't look at me like I'm some con.
你自己也不是什么好东西
You're as crooked as scoliosis.
我没有被抓到
I don't get caught.
你只能跟到这
This is as far as you go.
-别这样啊  老兄 -我们之间可没什么交情
-Come on,bro.-You and I,we're not bros.
你打算什么时候告诉我关于钱的事情?
When were you planning on telling us about the money,man?
什么钱?
What money?
就是韦斯特莫兰德那老头子 埋在犹他州沙漠里的500万美金
The $5 million that westmoreland planted in the desert in utah.
我找到斯蒂德曼了
I found stedman
我现在就和他在一起  林肯 他还活着
I'm with him now,linc.He's alive.
你说什么? 你找到斯蒂德曼了?
What are you talking about,you found stedman?
上帝啊
Oh,my god.
我的手在那个盒子里好久了 再不处理就要坏死了
my hand has been in that box for hours now- it is dying.
-我什么也不能承诺你 -那是我自己的事
-I can promise you nothing.- Story of my life.
这些?
These?
这是事先准备好的车钥匙
Keys to a car that's waiting for us
车就泊在几百码之外
a couple hundred yards from here.
是为两人还是五人准备的?
Are there two of us or five of us?
是我们两人的
That's the two of us.
有人来了
We got company.
他怎么会找到这来?
How did he know?
我们迟早会知道整件事的来龙去脉
It's only a matter of time before we know everything
在斯科菲尔德脑子里 有一套周密的出逃计划
that is in Schofield's head--
包括逃到哪 怎么个逃法
where he plans to run to   how he plans to get there--
等到时机成熟 他就会按照计划执行
so when the time comes   that he does get there,
到时候我们给他来个守株待兔
we'll be waiting for him.
加拿大和墨西哥边境巡警 都收到逃犯特写照片了
Canadian and Mexican border patrols have all the mug shots.
BORTAC(美边境特种部队) 高度戒备中
BORTAC's on high alert.
试试看能否联系到墨西哥边境巡警
See if we can get the Mexican Border Patrol
50里范围内再设置关卡
to set up checkpoints 50 miles in.
福克斯河狱长来电申请共同参与抓捕行动
The warden over at Fox River called,asked to be kept in the loop.
我该怎么应对他?
What should I tell him?
告诉他 他已经无权再管这事
That he's no longer in it.
你要的信息放在你办公桌上了
That info that you asked for is on your desk when you get in.
谢谢
Thank you.
下一步怎么走?
What's the plan,man?
没有强行规定过 随你便
No bars on these doors. Do what you like.
怎么做?
With what?
我们现在本该在墨西哥了
We're supposed to be in Mexico right now.
品着玛格丽塔鸡尾酒 等待酒精带来的刺激
sipping on margaritas, waiting for the heat to dip.
这就是原计划
That was the plan.
看到没 他们就是利用我们来挖洞
You see,they just used us to dig,man.
我们不过是钻地鼠而已
We're gophers, that's it.
-迈克尔在哪?  -他马上到
Where's Michael? He'll be here.
你知道吗,苏克雷?
Okay. You know what,Sucre?
或许我们可以联手搞定那笔钱
Maybe you and I should go and get that $5 million,
你明白我在说什么吗?
you know what I'm saying?
这笔钱就埋在犹他州的Tooele
I mean,it's just sitting there in Tooele,Utah
-期待重见天日 -难不成你还想呆在这儿?
ready to get some air. You want to stay here?
-那就闭上你的臭嘴! -你再敢碰我一次试试!
Then shut your mouth! You got one more time to touch me,man!
大家伙都冷静
All right,guys,chill.
-怎么冷静? -嘿!
What? Hey!
冷静
Relax.
亲爱的 你肯定行李都打包好了吗?
Honey,are you sure you packed everything?
真好吃
Yummy.
我们的照片登报了
Our photos are in the paper.
或许我们成了头版头条
We're probably all over the news.
对 你没有看到吗?
Yeah,and you didn't see that coming?
什么这么好笑?
What's so funny?
你们俩让我狂笑不止
The two of you cracks me up.
为我们登报干杯！
Here's to amateur hour;
你觉得呢?
what do you say,saludo?
对  对你个头 笑得那么白痴
Yeah,yuck it up,funny man.
最后的晚餐了
Last supper,boys.
吃完这顿咱们就分道扬镳了
This is the part where we say good-bye.
这虽然不多
It's not much.
足够让你起步了
It's enough to get you started.
嘿!呃...
Hey,uh...
我不会告诉你菲波纳奇在哪
no,I'm not telling you where fibonacci is.
我可没有问
Well,I didn't ask.
我仅仅是想要25美分打个电话
I only ask for a quarter for a phone call.
够你打四个的了
make farward
谢谢
Thank you.
我很想知道别的人怎样了
I wonder what happened to the other guys.
除了帝博格都开始了新路程
The all had a head start,except t-bag.
对  他一定血流成河
Yeah,he was,he was bleeding pretty bad.
你认为他死了吗?
Think he's dead?
搞定了没?
are you done?
还没有 我-我还要清洗一下伤口
No.I-I still have to clean it.
这么说已经搞定了?
But you're done?
是的
YeS.
是时候出发了
it's time to move
我们准备好了一切
We got everything we need.
先到犹他州短暂停留一下 然后马上出发去墨西哥
Just a quick stop in utah and then we're off to mexico.
LJ今天有个听证会
Lj has a hearing today
会决定他是否按成人犯罪那样量刑
to determine if he gets tried as an adult.
我能救出他
I can get hiM.
时机不对
It's not the right time.
那要等到什么时候?
When will it be?
等我们到墨西哥后 等我们在新闻的焦点里消失后
after we went to mexico  After we're off the news.
他被指控犯了两起杀人罪
They framed him for a double homicide.
一旦听证没有通过他会和成人罪犯关在一起
As soon as he loses his hearing,they're going to ship him out to an adult facility,
所以今天在法庭上是我救他的唯一机会
so today in the courthouse is my only chance to get him.
他们害死了维罗妮卡他们不能再夺走我的儿子
They took veronica,they're not going to take my son.
我明白
I know.
我能理解
我也绝不会丢下LJ不顾
I would - leave Ij behind
但是我们现在不能这么做
but we can't do this now.
事先根本没做过计划
There's no plan in place.
相信我 我对那法院很了解
Believe me,I know that courthouse.
我都记不清去过多少次
I've been there more times than I can remember.
看管他的只有一个法警
The only person guarding him's the bailiff.
他只配备了催泪弹和警棍
He carries mace and a big stick.
所以你打算暴力劫庭
So you're going to bum-rush the courthouse
那是你的计划?
that's your plan.
你真这么计划?
Are you serious?
是的
Yeah.
嘿 我们就要出发了
Hey,yo,we're headed out,man.
好吧  好运
Well,good luck .
祝大家都好运
to everyone
远离麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
那当然
Definitely.
别了 老兄
This is it,buddy.
老弟  我希望你能找到那女孩
I hope you find thgirl,buddy.
她是我的另一半 我会努力的
she is all i have.I will try
好运
Good luck.
放轻松点
You be easy,man.
一路平安(西班牙语)
Adios.
再见
See ya.
或许我们还能再见面
Maybe we'll see each other again.
谁知道呢 迈克尔
You never know,Michael.
天知道
Never know.
把你知道的关于法庭的一切都告诉我
Tell me everything you know about the courthouse.
睡过觉吗?
You get any sleep?
睡了几小时吧
A couple hours.
一下跑了八个 我到现在都无法相信
Eight of 'em, I still can't believe it.
这简直就是场"成人秀"安排娘们在军队工作
This is Exhibit "A" why you don't let women work in the military
在警局工作 尤其安排她们在男性监狱工作
the police force and especially inside a male prison, '
看看你都得到什么回报?
cause look what you get.
那娘们特意为她的相好斯科菲尔德不锁门
Dr. Sweetcheeks leaves the door open for
才会有接下来发生的一切
Schofield and here we are.
你这么说对某人不公平...
Sounds like there's a little bit more to the...
如果不是唐克雷蒂不锁门
If Tancredi doesn't leave her office door unlocked,
那八个混蛋这会儿 还不都乖乖呆在监狱内?
those eight dirtbags would in the shoe right now,okay?
这才是关键!
Bottom line!
布拉德
Brad.
有进展吗?
Any updates?
没有
None.
最后目击点在奥斯威戈的公墓内
They were last seen at that cemetery in Oswego.
-我们能抓到他们 -应该是他们能抓到他们
We'll get 'em. They'll get 'em.
这案子已经移交给FBI.
It's been handed over to the FBI.
那也不等于这件事我们就插不了手
Well,that doesn't mean we can't work it.
事实上就是不能管了
It does,actually
我们已经被抓捕小组除名
You and I have been pulled off the pursuit.
为什么?
Why?
我们本应该短时间内就抓捕归案的...
We're going to find out shortly.
我们必须向DOC总部报告 在那见吧
We have to report to the DOC headquarters.I will meet you there.
长官  我们能逮住这帮逃犯
Sir,we can get these guys.
只要再给我几天时间
Just give me a couple more days
-我发誓我能抓他们回来 -布拉德!
and I swear I'll get 'em. Brad!
我们必须去报告
We've got to go.
帕托塞克没有家庭? 什么相关线索都没有?
IVES: No family with Patoshik, nothing?
没错 大概四年前  都被他杀光了
Yeah,until about 4years ago.He killed all
阿克斯的信息更新过了
Updated rap sheet on Apolskis.
有时间看一下
Take a look when you get a chance.
非常抱歉
Oh...Man,I'm so sorry.
我的错 都是我的错
My bad. My bad,bro.
对不起
I'm sorry.
斯科特 科波莱内
Scott Kolbrenner.
就是这辆车了
It's this one here.
不要碰收音机
Don't touch the radio.
喂 你好 我是德 摩恩 赫莱德的律师
Yeah. Hi. I'm with the Des Moines Herald.
我负责LJ 布伦斯的听证会
I'm covering the LJ Burrows hearing.
听证会几点开始?
What time does that start today?
快点
Come on.
谢谢  3点开始
Thank you. 3:00.
听证会结束十分钟后他会被带到 转送站直到搭乘4点的车
The hearing lasts a half hour max.He'll be taken down to transport bay at ten till to catch the 4:00 van.
那么我们怎样才能接近他?
So how do we get close to him?
当我被铐上的时候 我什么也做不了
Well,when I was locked up, I had nothing to do
除了研究辩护状
except study the briefs.
尼克 萨维恩的律师号 是所有人当中最前面的
Nick Savrinn's bar number is on the front page of every one.
我们想和LJ说话
We want to talk to LJ, we just...
只需装扮成他的律师
We pose as one of his attorneys.
对呀
Yeah.
胡说八道! 这绝对是子虚乌有!
Hogwash.That is absolute hogwash.
请正面回答我的问题
Please answer the question.
斯科菲尔德怎么会有机会单独接触你
How was Scofield able to have exclusive access to you,
用小刀制住你 把你绑在椅子上   狱长大人?
pull a shank on you, and bind you to your chair--the warden of the penitentiary?
我相信了他
I trusted him.
很明显 他背叛了我的信任
Obviously, he betrayed that trust.
贝利克警官
Officer Bellick,
是不是所有逃跑 或者企图逃跑的犯人
is it true that almost all the inmates  who either escaped or tried to escape
都在监狱工厂干过活?
worked in Prison Industries?
没错
That's right.
为什么这帮犯人 在监狱工厂工作的同时
Why did these inmates have so much time to dig a hole
还有这么多时间挖洞?
in the floor of the guard's break room
-而且还是在警卫休息室的地板上挖? -这个我能告诉你答案
while working Prison Industries? I can answer that.With all due respect,
如果你们中的某个人 在监狱里工作过一天的话你就能明白
if any of you have ever worked a day in a prison,you would know that,
因为每个犯人每小时只能挣到19美分
since an inmate only gets 19 cents an hour,
所以肯定会磨蹭时间
some are bound to drag their feet.
贝利克警官
Officer Bellick,
你把管理监狱工厂的权利卖给出价最高的人 这是真的吗?
is it true you sold the right to run Prison Industries to the highest bidder?
当然不 哪个该死的对你说的?
No. Who the hell told you that?
这太难以置信了
This is unbelievable.
我们在这里浪费时间
While we're wasting time in here,
而外面还有八名罪犯在逃...
there are eight escaped convicts out there...
你是否曾经受雇于福克斯河 担任教化警官一职  盖瑞先生?
Were you employed at Fox River as a correctional officer, Mr. Geary?
-是的 -对 直到他因和犯人私下交易而被解雇
Yep. Yeah,until he was fired for shaking down inmates.
你最好别再这么暴怒 警官
That will be your last outburst,Officer.
你是否知道任何有关
Were you aware of any arrangement
贝利克警官与监狱工厂的犯人
Officer Bellick had
之间工作安排的内幕?
with any inmate regarding Prison Industries?
是的 他把这个权利卖给了约翰 阿布鲁奇
Yeah,he sold it to John Abruzzi.
约翰 阿布鲁奇
John Abruzzi--
那不是在逃犯之一吗?
who was one of the escaped convicts?
没错
Yep.
你再不配合 我们不得不考虑替换别的狱警
We'll get other C.O.s to substantiate this if we have to,
贝利克警官 我再给你次机会坦白交代吧
Officer Bellick, so I'm giving you one chance to get in front of it.
你有没有把管理监狱工厂的权利出售给约翰 阿布鲁奇?
Did you sell Prison Industries to John Abruzzi?
有还是没有?
Yes or no?
有 但是当时
Yes,but at no time
-我一点也不知道 -够了
was I aware of any talk That'll be all,
-贝利克警官 -有关逃跑的事
Officer Bellick. of escape.
够了!
That will be all!
狱长 你可以和贝利克在走廊候着
Warden,you and Officer Bellick can step out into the hallway.
我们商量好决定后再通知你们
We'll call for you when we've reached a decision.
我去喝点咖啡
I'm going to get some coffee.
这种情形下我已经竭尽所能
Well,I did my best under the circumstances.
好消息是你的手由于冰冻及时
The good news, sir,is you had the hand iced,
我可以把血管复原...
so I was able to restore blood flow and...
指骨还是有些弯曲
The bones are bent.
无论如何 我还是建议你尽快接受医疗护理
However,I recommend you get medical attention ASAP.
与此同时 吃一些阿司匹林
Meanwhile,some aspirin
有助于你降低血浓度 避免结块
will help thin the blood and avoid clotting.
还有些抗生素和止痛片
Some antibiotics and painkillers.
我经常会对宠物的主人说 把药片包上花生酱
I usually tell the owner of the dog, cat,whatever,to coat them with peanut butter
这样更方便咀嚼 但是很明显你不需要这么做...
so they're easier to chew but,obviously,in your case...
医生 你干的很棒
You did one hell of a job,Doc.
谢谢
Well,thank you.
你现在已经能够离开了
Well,uh... it's okay for you to leave now.
噢对  我要走了
Oh,I'm leaving.
但是你不能离开
You're not.
-什么? -你听到我说的
What? You heard me.
放心 我什么也没有看见
Look,sir, I haven't seen anything
我也不会对任何人提及
and I won't tell anyone.
你知道吗
Well,you know... you know,
我曾经栽过一次跟头
I fell for that bill of goods once before.
再也不会相信别人了
Never again.
我对天发誓决不对任何人提及
Sir,I swear to God I will tell nobody.
你会说的 那样我会在监狱中死去
You would,and I would die in prison.
求求你 求求你了
Please,please, please.
嘘!
Shh!
现在你乖乖听话
Now,you did me a solid,
这样我也可以回复温柔
so I'm going to return the favor.
你不反抗的话 我会很温柔的让你离开这个世间
This can go down humanely if you don't fight,
但是如果你再像刚才那样挣扎的话
but if you pull a stunt like that again,
那就别怪我不人道了
it's going to get inhumane right quick.
你来选择
Your call.
前者还是后者...
But,one way or another...
乖乖躺下吧 医生
I am putting you down,doc.
-小林肯 布伦斯 -我就是
LB's junia  yeah
进去吧 你有探访者
in here,you got a visitor
你就是LJ吧
You must be LJ.
FBI探员马宏
Agent Mahone,FBI.
谢谢
Thank you.
请坐
Please.
我想你一定听说了
I'm assuming you've heard.
说吧
Yeah.
我不得不告诉你
I have to tell you.
你父亲和叔叔的这次越狱...
What your dad and uncle pulled off...
给我留下非常深刻的印象
very impressive.
我在这方面干了14年
I've been doing this 14 years,
绝大多数的案件只能归类为偶然的运气
and most escapes can be attributed to dumb luck
或者暴力所为
or brute force.
就这件案子来看 计划的周密程度和复杂度
The level of planning and sophistication that went into this one,
一下逃跑了8个
and eight guys got out.
从专业的角度来说
I really do, professionally speaking,
我真的对林肯和迈克尔敬佩有加
have a lot of admiration for Lincoln and Michael.
酷 我们现在算朋友了
Cool. Now we're buddies.
你想要什么?
What do you need?
帮助我把他们带回来... 非暴力的手段
Help me bring them in... peacefully.
我不知道他们在哪
I don't know where they are.
我不知道他们会去哪
I don't know where they're going.
还有种方式你能帮助我
There's another way you can help.
怎么做?
How?
上电视
Go on TV.
我能让摄制组在半小时内赶到这
I can have a camera crew down here in a half an hour.
你知道吗?
You know what,man?
他们犯的谋杀罪冤枉到我父亲头上
The murder charge they put on my dad--
他们犯的另两起谋杀罪又嫁祸于我
the two murder charges they put on me--
这所有发生的一切 都来自上面的阴谋
Everything's been a setup coming from way up top.
因为你为政府卖命
So the fact that you work for the government--
我什么也不会说
I got nothing to say.
楼下工作人员会给你同样的建议
I'll give you the same advice that you'd get from the guy working
我再重复提醒你一遍
at the deli downstairs.
现在你该好好为自己考虑一下了
Start thinking about yourself now.
事实上 迟早都会面对到   没有人能够帮你渡过难关
In fact,the sooner the better, because no one--
不管你父亲还是你叔叔
not your father,LJ, not your uncle--is going to do your time.
你已经16岁了 会被量很长的徒刑
And,at 16 years old,you're looking at a long stretch.
你还有多少时间
How much time you get,
在哪服刑 狱友又会是谁
where you serve it, who your cell mate might be.
你得为自己考虑考虑了 现在就开始考虑吧
You need to start thinking about yourself.Now.
我想要你的父亲还有叔叔归案
I want your dad, I want your uncle,
我愿意等你来和我谈条件
and I'm willing to deal.
不要犹豫免得被别人抢了功劳
Don't wait and let someone else get the reward.
有事吗?
What's up?
嘿 你看上去很面熟啊
Hey,man, you look familiar.
是你主持上学期的大学联谊会吗？
Did you rush Sig Ep last semester?
Sig什么?
Sig what?
Sig Ep
Sig Ep.
-没有 -下一个
Nah. Next in line.
去哪?
Where to?
犹他州
Utah.
好了吗?
How we doing here?
明天才有班次
Nothing until tomorrow.
这样 我有45美金
All right,yo,I got 45 bucks.
最远能够去哪里?
How far will that get me?
尼克 萨维恩 律师号56437
Nick Savrinn. His bar number is 56437.
我要和我的客户LJ 布伦斯通一次话
I've got a call time with my client,an LJ Burrows
你好
Hello.
知道是谁吗?
Know who this is?
嗯
Yeah.
你好 尼克 萨维恩.
Yeah. Nick Savrinn.
最近挺难熬的吧?
How you holding on?
尽我所能
Doing what I can do.
你怎么样?
How about you?
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
我很难过你要去承受听证会
I'm sorry about what you're going through.
谢谢
Thanks.
要告诉你的是 呃...听证会后
Word is,uh... after this hearing,
由于我父亲最近太受关注
because of my dad being so high profile,they're...
他们要把我转移到亚利桑那州的 成人监狱"金曼"去
they're shipping me to an adult facility in Kingman,Arizona.
希望那不会发生
Yeah,well,hopefully, that ain't going to happen.
今天有没有和维罗妮卡联系过?
You hear from Veronica today?
她没有出现
She didn't show up.
那帮家伙分派了受命于法庭的 小丑们来参加我的听证会
They gave me some court-appointed clown.
没有 我没有联系她
No. I haven't heard from her.
今天有个探员过来和我谈话
Hey,this,uh...this fed came by and talked to me today.
然后呢?
Yeah?
他想让我帮忙
He wanted me to help try in getting
让我父亲现身
my dad to turn himself in.
他很了解你父亲 很可能真会发生
Well,knowing your dad, I doubt that's going to happen.
听好了LJ 接下去非常重要
Listen up,LJ. This is real important.
好的
All right.
在第三处  注意看Otis Wright
On the third,look out for Otis Wright.
记住了吗?
You got that?
在第三处  注意看Otis Wright
On the third,look out for Otis Wright.
到那个时候 把头一直抬着
Until then,keep you head up.
-什么? -记住就行
What? Just remember that.
我会尽我所能把你救出来
I'm going to do everything I can to get you out.
嘿 尼克... 如果你能碰到我爸
Hey,Nick... if you talk to my dad...
告诉他不管怎样 我都爱他
tell him no matter what, I love him.
联系上他了?
Did you get him?
我们去救人吧
Let's do this.
还有一站
Got one more stop.
在我的宗教里有种信仰
There is a belief in my religion
我知道肯定是真的
on which I know to be true
而且适用于每个人 不论是不是印度人
and it applies to everyone,Hindu or not.
我们此生的表现
The acts we commit in this life
决定了我们的来生
determine where we go in the next.
如果有人犯了罪恶 永远也别想
And he who commits evil can never hope
获得永恒的幸福
for eternal happiness.
不用再对我说教了 医生
Never been a goal  of mine,doc.
我就是个现实主义的人
I'm more a here and now type.
我来告诉你一些我所知的真相
I'll tell you something I know is true.
这儿的印第安人
The Indians here,
手握印地安战斧一族 在绝大多数人被屠杀之前
the tomahawk variety, some of them believe--well,used to
有些人相信 或者说曾经相信
believe before most of them were slaughtered--
当一个勇士在战场上杀死了另一个勇士
that when a warrior kills another in battle,
他吸取了倒下的勇士的灵魂
he absorbs that fallen warrior's spirit.
所以这并非是你的终点 医生
So this isn't the end for you,Doc.
你现在和我一体了
You're with me now.
这么好的天气 你过得如何?
And how are you doing this fine day?
我很好 你呢?
Uh,I'm great. How are you?
棒极了
Couldn't be better.
需要什么特别的东西 我能帮你找?
Anything in particular I can help you find?
-随便看看 谢谢
Just looking,thanks.
如果需要什么帮助 呼唤一声就行
Well,if you need any assistance, just give a holler.
-你好吗? -很好
How are this find day? Great.
需要我帮你找东西吗?
Can I help you find anything?
我很好 多谢
I'm good,thanks.
我们必须离开这
Hey. We gotta go.
我这就结账了
just need to pay up. Now.
警官 我能帮你什么吗
how are you today,officer?
对 他们就在里边
Yeah,they were right,uh...
怪了 刚才还在这边的
Well,they were-- they were right back here.
我们可以从这里步行去法院
We can make it to the courthouse on foot from here.
你不知道 所有的东西都在里面
You don't understand-- everything is in that car.
忘了这车吧 我们没时间了
Forget the damn car. We don't have time.
快点 我们出发了
Come on,man, let's go.
返家犹他行 寻同路搭车人 费用自理 联系黛布拉 珍
本局决定处罚如下
PAVELKA: It is the finding of this panel
狱长 珀尔扣除两周薪酬
that Warden Pope, you'll be docked two weeks
外加三个月观察期
placed on three months probation.
布拉德 贝利克
Officer Brad Bellick
辞退原职 立即生效
will be terminated-- effectively immediately.
贝利克先生
Mr. Bellick,
你可以收拾所有行囊
you can retrieve whatever belongings you may have
离开福克斯河了 处罚决定就这些
from Fox River; that will be all.
我在...我在福克斯河
I've... I've worked at Fox River
从18岁干起
since I was 18 years old.
做一名狱警是我生命的全部
Being a C.O. is my life.
我们很赞赏这点
And we appreciate that.
我们本能够节省很多时间
POPE: Look,you know,we could have saved a lot of time
如果一开始你就这么告诉我们的话
if you would have just told us in the beginning
那这就是在草率定罪
that this was going to be a railroad.
够了 狱长
That'll be all,Warden.
只有一个人
There is only one person
需要对越狱负责
responsible for this escape out there.
他的名字叫迈克尔 斯科菲尔德
His name is Michael Scofield.
而不是贝利克警官 更不是我!
It's not Officer Bellick. It's not me!
但是你们需要一个替罪羊 好吧
But you need a fall guy,fine.
但是你不能就这样要了他的饭碗
But you're not gonna be just taking Officer Bellick's job.
因为即使我不欣赏他的很多行为
Because even though I am not proud of many of his actions,
把矛头指向自己人
it will be a cold day in hell
会让人很寒心的
when I turn my back on one of my own men.
我不干了
I quit.
就这样吧
That will be all.
如果这件事情弄砸了
If this thing doesn't work out
你又会被关回福克斯河
and you end up going back to Fox River,
而我去不了了
I ain't coming to get ya.
我的意思是
I mean,
你是用脑思考的斯文人 我只是个会用拳头说话的粗人
you are the brains and I am the brute.
说真的 迈克尔
Seriously,Michael,
你完全可以不这么做
you don't have to do this.
行动吧
Let's go.
今天早上你接到尼克 萨维恩的电话
You got a call from Nick Savrinn earlier today.
都说了些什么?
What was that all about?
他是我的律师
He's my attorney.
-那是我的权利 -那就怪了
That's privileged. Hmm,that's odd
因为他被发现死在寓所内
because Nick Savrinn was found dead in his apartment
案发在给你电话一小时前
an hour before that call came in to you.
听好了LJ
Listen up,LJ,
接下去非常重要
this is real important.
在第三处  注意看Otis Wright
On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
记住了吗?
You got that?
你既然这么确信
You know for someone who's so convinced
政府能够不择手段
that the government is capable
栽赃陷害你
of so many underhanded things,
你还执意对我继续顽抗下去?
you sure are playing fast and loose with me.
你打算怎么做,
What are you going to do,
再往我身上加件冤案?
throw another fake murder charge on me?
谁是Otis Wright?
Who's Otis Wright?
我不知道
I have no idea.
我想你知道的
I think you do.
如果你不和我说实话
And if you don't tell me,
当你被判罪名成立后
after you're convicted,
我会到法庭上见证你被量刑
I will be in that courtroom when you're sentenced
让你不得好死
and I will hang you out to dry.
绝不是吓唬你
Take it to the bank.
帮我接通
Yeah,put me in touch
LJ 布伦斯案件的原告
with the prosecutor in the LJ Burrows case.
我想开个会
I want a meeting.
在三楼 注意Otis Wright  注:Otis Wright(发音同right右边)
On the third,look out for otis wright.
到那个时候 把头一直抬着
Until then,keep your head up.
奥的斯电梯公司
右边的Otis电梯
Otis wright.
走吧
Let's go.
等等
Hold on.
快进电梯
Move it.
等等
Hold on.
我来押送这孩子
I'll escort the boy.
Otis Wright 右边的Otis电梯
Otis Wright.Otis elevator on the right.
他打算怎么样?
What is he planning?
别掏枪 我不会伤害任何人
Keep it in the holster and no one gets hurt.
警告你别掏枪
Keep it in the holster.
好了LJ 按停止按钮
All right,LJ, hit stop.
他和我们一起走
He's coming with us.
保持冷静 冷静 超级警官
So just stay cool, super cop,stay cool.
嘿 小伙子 把他的枪递给我
Hey,buddy, give me his gun.
LJ 把手递给我
LJ,give me your hand.
抓住你了 孩子
That a boy.
加把劲
Come on.
嘿 退后!
Hey,back off!
退后! 快退后!
Back off! Back off!
你对谁都没有开枪 所以这次也不会开枪
You're not shooting anybody, neither are you.
放手吧 你的孩子能走路
Give yourself up and your kid can walk.
这是他离开这里的唯一途径
It's the only way he's getting out of this place.
-唯一途径! -爸爸!
It's the only way! Dad!
-爸爸 你必须放手 -不
Dad,you got to let me go. No
爸爸...
Dad..
你必须放手!
You got to let me go!
在上面  斯科菲尔德在这楼里 看住这孩子!
Up there. Scofield is in the building. Take him!
你们去那边 封住那路口
You guys go,cover that way.
斯科菲尔德还有布伦斯
Scofield and Burrows
就在这楼里!
are in the building!
站住! 别动!
MAN: Freeze! Do not move!
上卡车!
The truck!
布拉德利?
Bradley?
是我 妈妈
Yeah,Ma.
这么早回家干吗?
What are you doing home so early?
我今天休假...
I had to take...
在休假作废之前...
my personal day,you know, before they went away.
你不是应该去搜寻逃犯的吗?
Shouldn't you be looking for the convicts?
他们另外派人去了
They got somebody else doing that,Mom.
你没事吧?
You okay?
我很好
I'm good.
好吧
Okay.
哇！
Whoa.
大功快告成了
All right.
我想我们应该
I think we should break a bottle
开瓶香槟庆祝一下
of champagne across its bow.
如果你想把这东西带回家
If you're intending to get this thing home
庆祝结婚周年用 我可不推崇
for your anniversary tonight, I wouldn't recommend it.
听着 我想让你知道...
Listen,I want you to know I...
我感到能遇见你很幸运
well,I feel very fortunate to have met you.
我正在实施越狱
I'm breaking out.
我需要你确保
And you're going to make sur
我的兄弟能和我一起走
my brother goes with me.
欢迎您呼叫汽车之星 古戴特医生?
Thank you for calling AutoStar, Dr... Gudat?
不知道我发音是否正确?
Am I pronouncing that correctly?
呃...完全正确
Uh... dead on.
今天我能帮你什么吗?
How can I help you today?
我需要...路线方向指示
I need,uh... directions.
去哪里 先生?
Where to,sir?
犹他州
Utah.
打搅一下
Excuse me.
对不起吓到你了
I'm sorry.
你是斯科特 科波莱内吗?
Are you Scott Kolbrenner?
我是的
I am.
对了
Yeah.
你一定是黛布拉 珍吧
You must be Debra Jean.
-见到你很高兴 -我也是
It's nice to meet you. Yes,same here.
这太有意思了 因为我都打算出发了
It's so funny,'cause I was almost ready to leave when you called.
你居然打电话过来了 都没有其他人响应
No one else responded.
我猜想这儿犹他州的人不多 你是从那儿来的吗?
I guess there's not a lot of Utah people out here.Are you from there?
不是...我过去
No,I just,you know...
我过去就是为了...继承遗产
I'm headed up there to,uh... collect an inheritance.
我爷爷过世了
My grandpa died.
-哦 听到这很难过 -没关系
Oh,I'm sorry to hear that. It's all right.
爷爷是载着荣耀离去的
He went out with his boots on.
那你的行李呢?
So where's your stuff?
我昨天邮寄走了
Uh,I mailed it yesterday.
邮寄?
Mailed it?
我还从来没有听说过呢
I've never heard of that.
谁愿意顶着个行李包到处转悠
You know,you don't want to lug it around.
另外我还认识个UPS的家伙他就把行李弄走了
Plus,I got a boy who works for UPS,so he hooked it up.
你反悔让我搭乘了?
So you want to bounce?
没事 我的车就停在前面
Okay. I'm parked out front.
布拉德利?
Bradley?
什么事 妈妈
Yeah,Ma.
电视台刚刚宣布了悬赏
They just announced the rewards on the TV.
什么悬赏?
What reward?
针对罪犯的悬赏
The convicts.
就是那些越狱的逃犯
For the convicts-- the ones who escaped.
有多少?
How much?
每个悬赏10万美元
$100,000 apiece.
那个杀了莱娜斯总统 哥哥的家伙悬赏30万美元
$300,000 for the animal who killed President Reynold's brother.
整个国家的疯狂分子都会为
Every whacko in the country is going to be after
追求悬赏而拼了老命对吗?
those bums now, wouldn't you say?
警察！
Police!
举起手 走出卡车
Step out of the vehicle with your hands up.
我们必须继续跑
We got to move.
我不行了
I can't.
天哪
Oh,my God.
我辜负了他
I failed him.
对不起
Sorry. Sorry.
我辜负了他
I failed him.
我希望你准备好午餐
I sure hope you packed a lunch.
这里出发到亚利桑那州要好久
It's going to be a long ride to Arizona.
去吧
Move your ass.
派人去这附近所有的医院
Get men at all the area hospitals.
不管他们在哪里
Wherever they are,
有一个伤得很重
one of them's bleeding good.
那就意味着...
Which means...
要么自投罗网 要么坐以待毙
they either come to us... or they die.